<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Matthew Dillard</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Matthew Dillard</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/citations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/citations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;citations&#34;&gt;Citations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anderson, R. E., &amp;amp; Stevenson, H. C. (2019). RECASTing racial stress and trauma: Theorizing the healing potential of racial socialization in families. In American Psychologist (Vol. 74, Issue 1, pp. 63–75). American Psychological Association (APA). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1037/amp0000392&#34;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1037/amp0000392&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chen, Kaiping and Lee, Nathan and Lee, Nathan and Marble, William, How Policymakers Evaluate Online versus Offline Constituent Messages (November 30, 2018). &lt;a href=&#34;http://dx.doi.org/10.2139/ssrn.3251651&#34;&gt;http://dx.doi.org/10.2139/ssrn.3251651&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clear, James, author. Atomic Habits: Tiny Changes, Remarkable Results: an Easy &amp;amp; Proven Way to Build Good Habits &amp;amp; Break Bad Ones. New York, New York:Avery, an imprint of Penguin Random House, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/terragotchi__in-brief/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/terragotchi__in-brief/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;terragotchi&#34;&gt;Terragotchi&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tend to your own pocket-sized Earth by learning and practicing sustainable behaviors and mindsets, supported by constructive strategies for navigating climate anxiety.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Terragotchi is a concept app researched, designed, and developed between January-May 2025 as my Capstone Project for the UX Design Masters Program at the Maryland Institute College of Art. The app combines resource wiki, habit tracking, mindfulness, and virtual-pet gamification to educate, encourage, and strengthen sustainable lifestyles while providing guidance on navigating climate anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
